Minhazul Islam

An independent and self-motivated Computer Engineering student having prior experience on projects and tasks solving software and development-related problems. Hands-on experiences on Digital Marketing and SEO Expertise. Pursuit opportunities that will help me explore and enrich my learning enthusiasm and practice.





319/B-9, Senpara Parbata, Mirpur <u>- 1216, Dhaka</u>



minhazulislamsaif@gmail.com



+8801712080793

saifminhaz.github.io



in linkedin.com/in/saifminhaz



github.com/saifminhaz

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

American International University - Bangladesh

05/2017 - 12/2021

CGPA 3.50 out of 4.00

Thesis: Process Re-Engineering of Business Process Management System on Traffic System of Bangladesh.

Higher Secondary Certificate

Govt. M.M. College, Jashore

GPA 5.00 out of 5.00

Secondary School Certificate

Daud Public School, Jashore Cantonment, Jashore

2014

GPA 5.00 out of 5.00

Junior School Certificate

Daud Public School, Jashore Cantonment, Jashore

2011

GPA 5.00 out of 5.00

WORK EXPERIENCES

Ecomclips Limited (02/2022 - 07/2022)

IT Executive & Project Manager

Fireworks Communications & Consultancy Limited

(08/2022 - Ongoing)

IT Executive & SEO Expert

INTERNSHIPS

Introtuce Limited (07/2020 - 10/2020)

Junior Engineer

Global Chamber Dhaka (07/2021 - 09/2021)

Project Manager

IPDC Finance Limited (09/2021 - 12/2021)

IT Executive

SKILLS



INTERETS

Full Stack Development Tech Enthusiast **Network Security** Operating System System Administrator **Table Tennis**

PERSONAL PROJECTS

IPDC Inventory Management System (IIMS)

IPDC Finance Limited

Full Complete Web Based Application

Car Parking Management System (Parkit)

Project On Website Technology

Full Complete Web Based Application

Data Store Management System (DSMS)

Project on WebTech and Advance database Full Complete Web Based Application

Hospital Management System (HMS)

Project On Website Technology Full Complete Web Based Application

Car Parking Management System (Parkit)

Full Complete Software on C#

Banking Management System (BMS)

Project on Java

Full Complete Software on JAVA

Ecommerce Website: KBFMore

Clients Project on Ecomclips

Full Complete Ecommerce Website on Shopify

Ecommerce Website: Closed Door Liquidation

Clients Project on Ecomclips

Full Complete Ecommerce Website on WordPress

ACHIEVEMENTS CERTIFICATIONS

Coursera (04/2020 - 10/2020)

108 Certificates on Different Courses and Projects

CCNAv7: Switching, Routing, and Wireless

Essentials (03/2021 - 05/2021)

Passing grade from Networking Academy instructor and final exam.

CCNAv7: Enterprise Networking, Security, and

Automation (05/2021 - 07/2021)

Passing grade from Networking Academy instructor and final exam.

Red Hat System Administration II (RH134)

(02/2022 - 06/2022)

Red Hat System Administration I (RH124) (02/2022 - 04/2022)

LANGUAGE APTITUDE TEST

IELTS: 7.0

Speaking: 7.5 Listening: 7.5 Writing: 6.0 Reading: 6.5